Okay.
I'm as the foot of the ladder, the lamb birthday is our only
gift for us in the surface of about 1 or 2 inches.
Although the surface appears to be very, very fine green
as you get close to it. It's almost like a powder.
The ground mist is very fine.
And then along.
Okay, I'm going to leave that one foot up then.
Both hands down about the fourth wrong up.
There you go.
I think all of the same.
But there is a red supply that will read the flag that's on the front
landing gear of this lamb.
There's two hemisphere one showing each of the two
hemisphere's earth underneath which is here man from the planet earth for
except for it upon the moon.
July 1969, AP.
AP came in deep.
I guess you're about the only person around.
It doesn't have TV coverage of the sea.
That's right, I don't move any bit.
How is the quality of the TV?
Oh, it's beautiful Mike, really is.
Okay, that's great. Is the lighting halfway down?
Yes indeed. They've got the flag up now and you can see the stars
and stripes on the left.